Elizabeth Lissner

Software Engineer - Saint Louis, Missouri 314-435-6298 – eswalker0723@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/elizabeth-lissner-se/ - github.com/EllieLissner - portfolio

I am a team-oriented software developer with a Doctorate of Pharmacy and an eagerness to learn new skills and technologies. Strengthened by my experience in the medical field and attention to detail, I employ my skills in Javascript and Express.js to create fully functional full stack web applications. I love problem solving, and I often think on and discuss interesting roadblocks even when not actively coding. I am thrilled to bring my enthusiasm for teamwork and learning to a position where I can continue to grow.

SKILLS

Languages - JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Python | Libraries and Frameworks - React.js, Node.js, Bootstrap Database - PostgreSQL, Sequelize, MongoDB, Mongoose | Other - RESTful Routing, JSON, Express

PROJECTS

Picture Saver July 2021

(Typescript, React.js, Postgres, Sequelize, Node.js, AWS S3) Created full stack web app, utilizing Typescript React.js for the front end, that allows the user to upload files to Amazon's Simple Storage Server, while simultaneously saving some of that data to an individual database within Postgres for later retrieval.

Falendar June 2020

(MongoDb, Mongoose, Express, React.js, Node.js) Worked with a team to create a functional calendar app that highlights the daily itinerary. Created with React font end with functioning calendar and event creation. Back end created with MongoDb and Mongoose to save calendar entries to an online database.

Motivational Puppy May 2021

(Node.js, Postgres, Sequelize, RESTful routing) Full stack web app to make motivational posters using random pictures and quotes provided by public APIs. Utilized RESTful routing with Express.js through the backend and then utilized Postgres, and Sequelize for database management to save and edit posters.

EXPERIENCE

Social Media Manager

January 2020- January 2021

Progressive Broadband | Crossville, TN

- Analyzed coverage maps and leads for potential business expansion into new markets. Collaborated with the President regarding moving into new markets based on density of potential client interest
- First point of contact for 95% of new leads who contacted the company for requests for service either on social
 media or through the company contact page. Investigated each new lead for candidacy for service, informed of
 plans and pricing, and scheduled installs and site surveys, all while maintaining a professional and positive
 atmosphere.
- Coordinated site surveys and equipment installs between the customer and the install team. Maintained contact with the customer if the install team was running late or a reschedule was necessary.

Staff Pharmacist December 2015 - May 2017

Jazz Pharmaceuticals | Saint Louis, MO

- Evaluated prescriptions for accurate patient, physician, and medication information and ensured compliance with state and federal law with 99% accuracy rate
- Translated difficult medical jargon into common language for complicated specialty medication for 15-20 patients daily.
- Educated patients on how to safely administer this unusual medication, avoid interactions with other medicines, foods, and drink, and ensured understanding by asking questions of the patient so they demonstrate understanding.

EDUCATION

Full-stack Software Engineering Immersive student in an intensive, twelve-week, 450+ hour program focused on product development fundamentals, object-oriented programming, MVC frameworks, data modeling, and team collaboration strategies. Developed a portfolio of individual and group projects.

Doctorate of Pharmacy (Pharm.D.)

September 2008- May 2014

Saint Louis College of Pharmacy | Saint Louis, MO